# Seunghwan Hong

harrydrippin@gmail.com github.com/harrydrippin +82 10-4550-9287

#### **Summary**

I'm a software engineer of Common Computer and undergraduate student of Kookmin University. I enjoy to learn various things and love to try and challenge new things. Currently I'm working on Al Network, blockchain network for distributed computing like learning AI or running research purposed codes. My research area includes open source, deep learning, information security, blockchain.

#### **Professional Experience**

### Common Computer (Al Network), Software Engineer

Sep. 2018 – Present

- Build AI Network web interface and backend for executing distributed computing job with AIN, Ethereum based token for using our service.
  - Implement REST API, Socket based services for communicating between user and distributed blockchain members who are participating to the network as a computing node.

Web3, Chrome Extension, Typescript, React.js, Express.js, Firebase Realtime Database, S3

### BinaryVR, Software Engineer Internship

Jun. 2018 - Aug. 2018

- Build framework for managing and annotating dataset
  - Implement REST API, Socket based services for communicating between user and data server. Valid landmark, tongue, and face checker, misaligned image collector, landmark annotator, etc. Typescript, Node 10, OpenCV for Node, React.js, Express.js, Redis, DynamoDB, S3
- Deep learning model testing platform based on web app
  - Implement asynchronous P2P direct connection between web browser and model server. WebRTC, Python 3, asyncio
  - Implement Javascript DL model class for visualizing landmarks on the real-time camera input. WebAssembly, Emscripten, React.js

### Jininsa Company, Software Engineer

- Rule-based chatbot decision framework
  - Implement a framework to make the fitting conversation with users for various situations like singing songs, reading books, end-to-end game, etc. Python 3, SQL, Redis, Docker

RESTful API server framework for mobile application

- Implement API services for communication with chatbot server and managing user information. Flask, Redis
- Containerize all infrastructures and make a set of scripts for controlling containers. Docker, Shell script

#### **South Korea Government's R&D Business, Project Manager, Lead Developer** Jun. 2016 - Dec. 2016

- Middle language for block-based programming language
  - Design core concept of language; abstracting one code to another three representation based on user level.
  - Implement language compiler which compiles 'Mocca' code to parse tree and Python. C#, Compiler-Compiler

#### **Technical Skills**

Languages: Python 3, Typescript, Javascript (fluent); C++, Java (working knowledge)

Frameworks / Platforms: Express.js, Flask (Python 3.x), React.js, Vue.js, AWS, Terraform, Docker

Other Skills: Agile style, Slack, Atlassian Stack (JIRA, Confluence, Bitbucket), Jupyter Notebook, Sketch, Zeplin

Jun. 2017 - Dec. 2017

#### **Education**

### Kookmin University (Seoul, South Korea)

Mar. 2016 - Present

Undergraduate in Computer Science, Average in Major: 3.86 / 4.5

#### **Publications**

Case of Social Contribution Project using Open Source Software Development Principle, **Seunghwan Hong,** Gihyeon Yang, Seongkwon Yoon, Dujin Jeong, Jaeyoung Park, Soochurl Shin, Minsuk Lee, Korea Computer Congress 2018 (KCC 2018), Jeju, South Korea, 2018.

Studying OPEG Score Development for Learning Open Source Software Development Practice, **Seunghwan Hong**, Dong-Gyu Kim, Geon Son, Domin Kim, Soochurl Shin, Dujin Jeong, Rina Choi, Minsuk Lee, Korea Computer Congress 2017 (KCC 2017), Busan, South Korea, 2017.

#### **Honors and Awards**

### Prize for Best Engineering, 23rd Startup Weekend

Apr, 2017

I made sort of system for managing hackathon and evaluating Git projects to exact number of score.

### 1<sup>st</sup> Place (South Korea Government R&D Business)

Dec, 2016

I successfully completed my projects and achieved the overall first grade in this business.

### 4<sup>th</sup> Place (National Competition), 2015 Korea Olympiad in Informatics

Oct, 2015

I built new educational programming language which can program with Korean letters.

#### **Contributions and Invited Talks**

### **Openhack: National Union of Engineering School Hackathon**

2017

Organizer & System Developer

### Google Developer Group: Korea, Campus Summer Party

2017

Technical Session: Invited speaker ('Reactive Programming for Beginners')

## **Volunteering Experience**

#### Colored by Software, Lead Member of Technical Staff

May. 2016 – present

Non-profit software education voluntary service that educates software to people who are interested in software in the library all over the country. Volunteered as a system developer for this project and built library searching system, lecture searching system, and landing page.